迈克:嗨,妈妈.
Mike: Hey.Mother.
麦琪:不许你出去逛悠了.
Maggie: Your tour has just been cancelled.
迈克:我还以为你们今晚会工作很晚.
Mike: I thought you were working late tonight.
麦琪: 确实很晚.
Maggie: I did.
迈克:盘子都是我洗的,你的晚饭是我放到炉子里的,这样,
Mike: Well, you'll be pleased to know that I did all the dishes and put
在一整天的辛苦工作之后,回到家中,
your dinner in the oven so it would be nice and warm for you when you
你会感到舒适,温暖.知道这些您会很高兴吧.
got home from a long hard day at the paper.
开萝尔:是我洗的盘子,是我把你的晚饭放到炉子里的.
Carol: I did the dishes, and I put your dinner in the oven.
迈克:好,那是谁告诉你这么的呢?
Mike: Yeah, well who told you to do it?
麦琪:谢谢你,开萝尔.你爸爸在厨房么?
Maggie: Thank you Carol.Is your dad in the kitchen?
爸爸:不,他出去了,把家交给我负责.
Mike: No.He's gone and left me in charge.
开萝尔:哧!
Carol: Hu!
麦琪:他在哪儿?
Maggie: Where is he?
迈克:在本的学校,开母亲俱乐部会议.
Mike: He's at Bens school at the mothers club meeting.
麦琪:今晚.
Maggie: tonight.
迈克:我知道对你来说会惊讶,我也一样,妈妈.
Mike: I know.It sounds a little shaky to me too mum.
麦琪:这篇报导让我忙得不可开交,会议的事全忘到脑后了.
Maggie: I'm so busy with this story, the meeting completely slipped my mind.
迈克:也就是说,你相信他么?
Mike: So you believe him?
麦琪:当然.难道我不应该相信他么?
Maggie: Of course.Why shouldn't I?
迈克:是这样的,这篇报导让你忙得不可开交,而时间长了男人会感觉有些寂寞.
Mike: well you know, you've been a little busy with the paper and a man
can get to feel lonely after a while
麦琪:迈克*艾伦*希佛.你想说什么?
Maggie: Michael Aaron Seaver.What are you suggesting?
迈克:想说的就是一个男人,他离开了自己的家,
Mike: That a man who leaves him home with two dozen home made fudge surprise
带着两打家里自制的奶油咖啡饼,一定没什么好事.
brownies, is up to no good.
麦琪:嗨,本.
Maggie: Hi Bennie.
本:嗨.
Ben: Hi.
麦琪:我十岁的心肝宝贝,最近还好么?
Maggie: How's my favorite ten year old on the planet?
本:我很好.
Ben: I'm good.
麦琪:很高兴看到你在做家庭作业,但是,
Maggie: It's nice to see you doing your homework,
你的睡觉时间是不是已经过了?
but isn't it passed your bed time?
本:对,我一直在等你.
Ben: Yeah, I was waiting up for you.
麦琪:好了,那你就再等我会儿,
Maggie: Well, why don't you stay up a few more minutes and keep my company
陪着我吃点东西.
while I eat.
本:太好了.看,我在艺术课上做的.
Ben: Great.Look what I made in art class.
麦琪:哇!多有声势吧.
Maggie: Wow!How stylish.
本:对,如果我需要,这东西不会伤害我.
Ben: Yeah, and if I need, that stuff won't hurt me.
麦琪:他们认识你,本.
Maggie: They know you Ben.
本:那你有照片么,我可以放进去的?
Ben: So do you have a picture I can put in it?
麦琪:你想要我的照片?
Maggie: You want my picture?
本:对.
Ben: Oh yeah.
麦琪:本杰明,这真是我莫大的荣幸.
Maggie: Gee Benjamin.This is quite an honor.
本:而且也非常的实际.
Ben: And practical too.
麦琪:实际?
Maggie: Practical?
本:对.我想,有了你的照片我就不会太想你了,
Ben: Sure.I figure with your picture I won't miss you so much.
即使当你工作很晚的时候也是如此.好了,你今天过得怎么样?
Even when you work late.So, how was your day?
杰森:麦琪!
Jason: Maggie!
麦琪:在屋里这儿.
Maggie: In here.
杰森:嗨,亲爱的,对不起,我晚了.
Jason: Hi honey.Sorry I'm late.
麦琪:我相信,参加母亲俱乐部的母亲们都喜欢吃我做的奶油咖啡饼吧?
Maggie: I trust that the mothers at the mother's club enjoyed my fudge surprise brownierecipe
杰森:是的,的确.不过会议有点乱哄哄的,无果而终.当我们讨论到学校狂欢节的安排的时候,梅林达*福瑞斯特说,"我们今年不打算参加短跑项目了,因为活动剧烈太受不了了".朱迪*琼斯说,绝对不行;梅林达说,对我无所谓.于是,朱迪火了,她跳起来,跃过桌子,卡住梅林达的喉咙.然后,把她掀翻在地,两下三下.我们把她们拉开.东西到处都是.我只不过是在开个玩笑.
Jason: Yes, they did.Well the meeting kind of bobbed down though, when we got
on to the plans for the school carnival and Melinda Forrest said "we're going to
have to drop the dart group this year because it's just all together too violent
Well, that Judy Jones thing, so she said over my dead body, and Melinda says
that's fine to me.Well Judy freaks, rahh, and she leaps over the desk, grabs
Melinda by the throat and starts throttling her.Then throws her down, two three.We're
pulling bodies apart.There s make up everywhere.I'm just kidding
麦琪:我知道.你以为我还那都不知道啊?
Maggie: I knew that.Do you think I didn't know that?
杰森:麦琪,是我冒犯你了么,还是你有一点紧张?
Jason: Maggie, am I off base here, or are you a little tense?
麦琪:你怎么知道我紧张了?
Maggie: What makes you think I'm tense?
杰森:你正在出汗,你从来不这样除非你紧张的时候.
Jason: Well you are soaking, and you never prune out like this unless there's tension
麦琪:既然你真的这么了解我,那你为什么不告诉我,
Maggie: Well if you know me so well Jason,
作为一个母亲我很失败?
why didn't you let me know that I was failing as a mother?
杰森:那该死的门铃是不是在响?
Jason: Is that the darn door bell?
麦琪:难道你不会告诉我,我作为一个母亲并不失败么?
Maggie: Aren't you going to tell me that I'm not failing as a mother?
杰森:当然不,麦琪.作为母亲,你一点儿也不失败.
Jason: Of course Maggie.You're not failing as a mother.
麦琪:不要一副恩赐的样子和跟说话.
Maggie: Don't patronize me.
杰森:今天你是不是被炒了,还是怎么着?
Jason: Did you get fired today, or something?
麦琪:没有啊.公司里每个人都喜欢我.
Maggie: No.At work everybody loves me.
杰森:好了吧,我要出去把我的沃尔沃洗一洗,然后回屋睡觉.
Jason: Well, before I turn in, I think I'll go buff the Volvo.
麦琪:呆在家里,还有了,
Maggie: At home, on the other hand,
本需要把我的照片放在身边,好记得我的模样.
little Ben has to carry a picture of me to remember what I look like.
杰森:麦琪,放在本身边的是兰博的照片.
Jason: Maggie, Ben carries pictures of Rambo.
麦琪:母亲俱乐部会议的事情我忘得一干二净.
Maggie: I totally forgot about the mothers club meeting.
杰森:想听听留言么?
Jason: Do you want a massage?
麦琪:所以我找了,结果找到了这个.念念这个.
Maggie: Then I find this.Read this.
杰森:免了吧,还是你来帮我念吧.
Jason: You might have to help me here Mag.
Maggie: It's a letter form the Wendell Wenkie elementary school mothers club
第一行写的是各位母亲们,
And the first line says fellow mothers, and it's addressed to you.
可是地址收信人是你.
An official body of the long island school system recognizes you as Ben's
长岛学校系统内的官方机构居然认定你是本的母亲.
mother.
杰森:你也知道啊,麦琪,我们都是些女人.开玩笑呢.
Jason: Well you know Maggie, we're just a bunch of women.It's a joke.Come on.
好了.笑声是……让紧张自然放松的最佳方法.来,试一试.
Laughter is the best way of releasing tension naturally.Come on try it.
哈哈哈哈哈.好了,下面正经点儿,
Ha ha ha ha ha .Ok, get serious for a minute then.
就一小会儿.麦琪,如果你还是不开心,那我就得毙了你.
Maggie if you don't lighten up, I'm going to have to shoot you.
麦琪:你最好的招数就那些是么?
Maggie: Is that the best you can do?
杰森:还有橡皮鸡没说呢.
Jason: Well, without a rubber chicken, yeah.
麦琪:杰森,我期待已久的是中恳的建议,比方,"麦琪,
Maggie: Jason, I expected some sound advice, like "Maggie,
让工作融化你失败的感觉".干点正事,多和本待在一起.
put your feelings of failure to work." Do something, spend more time with Ben.
主动去帮他张罗狂欢节的事儿,让他知道你是关心他的.为什么不这样去做呢?
Volunteer for his carnival so he knows I care.Why not.That is a great idea.
这是个好主意,而且简单易行.杰森,你为什么不能想想这些呢?
It is so good.It's so simple.Jason, why didn't I think of this?
杰森:你请指教,欢迎.
Jason: You're welcome.
麦琪:亲爱的,我没有显摆自己的意思,
Maggie: Honey I am not showing off.
我刚才只是觉得好心烦啊.
I just felt like killing six hours and whipping up a batch of bucklum.
默特:杰森.
Murtle: Yoo hoo!Jason.
杰森:嗨.
Jason: Hi.
女士们:哦!杰森!你行啊.
Ladies: Oh!Jason!You made it.
杰森:还记得么?我妻子.
Jason: You remember my wife?
格尔:当然记得.这位是安妮.
Gale: Oh of course.Annie.
麦琪:嗨,安妮.
Maggie: Hi Annie.
格尔:不,我是格尔.
Gale: No, I'm Gale.
默特:嗨.
Murtle: Hi.
麦琪:麦琪.
Maggie: Maggie.
默特:不,我叫默特.
Murtle: No I'm Murtle.
朱迪:姑娘们,姑娘们,赶快坐好.
Judy: Girls, girls, let's grab our seats.Ok.
我们有许多关于逛欢节的事情要商量,之后,有美味儿的点心等着大家,
We have a lot of carnival business to discuss before we can get to those
有的还冒着热汽儿呢.好了,上次讨论过的问题?
luscious, tantalizing, very succulent desserts.Some of which are still warm.
有么?请讲,格雷斯.
So, any old business?Yes Gracey.
格雷斯:我想告诉杰森,他的方法我试过了,
Gracey: I just wanted to tell Jason that I tried his rump roast marinade
我们全家都非常地喜欢.
recipe, and my whole family just adored it.
杰森:哦,很好.
Jason: Oh good.Well if you want to have some real excitement next time,
如果下次您想做得更好,就把你的肉泡上两整天.
try soaking your rump for two full days.
朱迪:好了,新的问题?有么?首先,我认为……请讲.
Judy: Ok, any new business?First of all I think... Yes
麦琪:大家好,我是麦琪*希佛,
Maggie: Hello, I'm Maggie Seaver and I'm the other Seaver mother.
另一家姓希佛的,我是孩子的母亲.
And I just wanted to say that I'd be happy to volunteer to help out at
我想在周六逛欢节上来帮忙做志愿者,我会很乐意这么做的.
Saturday's carnival.
女士们:哦!(鼓掌)
Ladies: Oh!(Applause)
杰森:精神可嘉!
Jason: Bravo!
麦琪:我有点晚了,这我心里有数.
Maggie: And I know I'm a little late,
不过,因为这次是为了孩子的学校筹集资金,
but since this is to raise money for our kid's school,
十分重要,有什么我能帮忙的么?
I know how important it is, anything I can do to help.
Judy: Oh!That is the Wendell Wilkie spirit.Come on ladies
麦琪*希佛,你请上前面来!
Maggie Seaver you come on down! Oh, you need to get with Gracey Thornton.
和格雷斯一起.她是我们狂欢节的主席.有请格雷斯.
She's our carnival chairman.Chairperson.Yes Gracey.
格雷斯:我提议由麦琪*希佛接替我担任狂欢节主席.
Gracey: I just want to move that I be replaced as carnival chairperson
by Maggie Seaver.
女士:同意.
Lady: I second that motion.
麦琪:不,我真的是……
Maggie: No, see that I really...
朱迪:支持者请喊"I"
Judy: All in favor say 'I'
所有人:"I".
Everyone: 'I'
杰森:对不起,"I".
Jason: Sorry, 'I'.
麦琪:不.
Maggie: No.
朱迪:提议通过.麦琪*希佛担任新的狂欢节主席.好了,
Judy: Motion carried.Maggie Seaver is the new carnival chairperson.
如果没有事情,休会.开吃.
Ok, with no other business before me, this meeting is adjourned.Let's eat.
麦琪:请稍等片刻.
Maggie: Wait a minute.
朱迪:什么事?
Judy: Why?
麦琪:我对如何做好狂欢节主席职一无所知.
Maggie: I don't know anything about being a carnival chairman.
朱迪:主席.(注:谐音,双关.Chairman,chairperson)
Judy: Chairperson.
麦茜:其实非常非常地简单.
Macey: It's really very simple.
朱迪:你是不是需要帮助.
Judy: I thought you wanted to help.
麦琪:对,确实要,
Maggie: yes I do, but...
可是……狂欢节委员会里有没有人以前做过这类工作?
Is there any one on the carnival committee who has done this before?
朱迪:狂欢节委员会.非常好的主意.
Judy: Carnival committee.What a wonderful idea.
杰森:啊,朱迪.我提议麦琪退场.
Jason: Ah Judy.I move that we let Maggie off the hook here.
女士:同意.
Lady: I second that.
麦琪:稍等.
Maggie: Wait a minute.
诸位中有多少已经志愿为本次狂欢节服务?
How many of you have volunteered to work on the carnival?
那好,大家都这样一种态度,
Well with this attitude,
我很奇怪怎么没有人提议彻底取消此次狂欢节呢?
I'm surprised somebody hasn't moved to cancel the whole carnival.
女士:同意.
Lady: I second that motion.
麦琪:停.就是说,我们大家都太忙了,
Maggie: Stop it.So this means we are all too busy to help the children.
来不及帮助孩子们.是这样么?那好,
Is that it?Well look.I'm busy too but I am going to make the time.
我也很忙,但是我一定会把时间挤出来.你们的事情到底有多重要,就丢不开么?
What do you all have to do that's so important?The cooking?The laundry.
做饭?洗衣服?家务?
The housekeeping.
麦茜:目前我正在州是高法院出庭辩护.
Macey: I'm arguing a case before the state supreme court.
麦琪:好.那,其它人呢?
Maggie: Ok.But what about the rest of us?
杰森:我报名做志愿者.
Jason: I'll volunteer.
麦琪:噢,是位非常忙碌的男士.
Maggie: And this is a very busy man.
麦琪:对,我是名精神病科大夫.
Jason: Yes.You know I'm a psychiatrist.
我一天工作达八小时.
I could spend up to eight hours a day, on my anal retentives alone.
麦琪:我们能不能不在这个地方提什么是重要什么是不重要?孩子,
Maggie: Aren't we all forgetting what's important here.The children.
我们来这儿就是为了他们.难道我们真的想一直坐在这里,
They are why we're here.
无所事事,
Are we really all going to sit here and let our kids down,
让孩子们失望么,尤其是在他们最需要我们的这个时候?
just when they need us the most?
女士:我报名.
Lady: I volunteer.
女士:我也报名.
Lady: Me too.
麦琪:很好.
Maggie: Great.
女士:我报名.
Lady: I'll volunteer.
麦茜:哦,让我的客户见鬼去吧.
Macey: Oh, to heck with my client.Let him fry.
(该周晚些时候)
(Later that week)
开萝尔:不停地搅动,开萝尔.
Carol: Keep stirring Carol.
一碗这样的辣椒会给本的学校赚一块钱.
This chilly is going to bring Ben's school a dollar a bowl.
开萝尔:如果把辣椒免费分发,而后收10块钱胃药钱,
Carol: You could raise a lot more by giving this stuff away and charging
赚得更多.
ten dollars for antacid tablets.
本:嗨,哇,多好的东西啊.
Ben: Hi.Wow, what neat stuff.
麦琪:不碰,本.这都是你们学校狂欢节的奖品.
Maggie: Oh don't touch those Ben.Those are grab bag prizes for your carnival.
迈克:如果这不是上帝的礼物就好了.
Mike: Well if this isn't a gift from god.
本:哇!
Ben: Wow!
开萝尔:妈妈,一个巨大的泡泡正在形成.
Carol: Mum.A huge bubble is forming.
杰森:麦琪,来看这个.
Jason: Maggie, come and see this.
麦琪:迈克,告诉你爸爸,我忙着呢.
Maggie: Mike, tell your dad I'm busy.
迈克:她在忙,爸爸.
Mike: She's busy dad.She's lancing a grease pocket.
麦琪:本,往后退.本!这告诉过你了,那些是奖品.
Maggie: Ben, step back.Ben I told you those were prizes.
杰森:瞧,查理为拍卖会捐了什么东西.
Jason: Look what Charlie Bubus donated to the auction.
麦琪:好了,把它放在拍卖箱旁边.
Maggie: Well put it by the auction box.
本:双臂断了的塑像,有谁会来买?
Ben: Who's going buy a statue with the arms busted off?
开萝尔:本,你可真是个行家.
Carol: Ben, you're a real aficionado.
本:把你的话收回去.
Ben: Take that back.
迈克:本,不要吵了.为了准备你的狂欢节,我有一大堆事要做呢.
Maggie: Ben, no arguments.I have a lot to do to get ready for your carnival.
本:可是,妈妈,她骂我是傻子.
Ben: But mum.She called me a fish.
麦琪:本,我说过了,不要再吵了.我们做这些都是为了你.
Maggie: Ben, I said no arguments.We are doing all this for you.
如果你帮不上忙,没关系,至少你不要碍事.
If you can't help, you can at least stay out of the way.
迈克:对,我们正在这儿工作呢.
Mike: Yeah.We're working here.
开萝尔:妈妈,辣椒给糊了.
Carol: Mum.The chilly just burped.
麦琪:那说明,烧好了.
Maggie: That means it's ready.
麦琪:所有这一切好棒啊.我们有那么多客人,
Maggie: All this is wonderful.
聚集在外面,那今晚上我们会尽兴而欢的,或者翻天覆地.
We have a huge crowd gathering outside, so we're either
going to have a festival, or riot
杰森:220伏保险烧了,110伏的正常,一切准备完毕.
Jason: Well, I've got the two twenty split up,
好像我还明白我在干什么,是吧?
I've the one ten all fired up and ready to go.
好了,大家听好了,加电.
Sounds like I know what I'm doing.Doesn't it?Alright everybody, hit.
所有人:哦,杰森.耶……(没电)哦!
Everyone: Oh Jason.Yeah!...(power fails) oh!
杰森:幸亏我管的不是核电.可能是哪儿没连好,
Jason: Well at least be thankful I'm not running a nuclear power plant.
我去看看.
Just a shortsomewhere.I'll take care of it.
麦琪:大家准备好了么?
Maggie: Ok.Ok, everybody ready?
接吻女士:接吻准备好了.
Kissing Lady: Kissing booth ready.
迈克:扑克准备好了.
Mike: Poker booth ready.
麦茜:飞镖准备好了.
Macey: Dart booth ready.
女士:棉花糖准备好了.
Lady: Cotton candy booth ready.
开萝尔:我非得戴这帽子么?
Carol: Do I have to wear this hat?
女士:化妆间准备好了.
Lady: Face painting booth ready.
麦琪:好,克莱贝尔,拍卖准备好了么?哦,
Maggie: Oh good work Clarabelle.Now what about the auction booth?
是我负责的.好了,拍卖准备完毕.
Oh I'm running that.Ok auction booth ready.
朱迪:我这边需要帮忙.
Judy: I need help with my what-cha-ma-call-it booth.
接吻女士:我可以调几个我这儿的男士过去.
Kissing Lady: I could use some male lips in my booth.
杰森:好了.再来一次,合闸.
Jason: Alright.Hit it again Earl.
所有人:耶!哦!哇!
Everyone: Yeah!Oh!Wow!
麦琪:杰森,你没事的话,我们这边需要人手.
Maggie: Jason, if you're through, we need some help on the booths.
接吻女士:在边儿呢,杰森.
Kissing lady: Over here Jason.
胖女士:哦,杰森.帮帮我哦!
Fat Lady: Oh Jason.Help me!
杰森:该怎么做,究竟该怎么做.看来我得牺牲我的男色了.
Jason: What to do, what to do.Well it's time I lent my lips to charity.
麦琪:你必须招惹她是么?
Maggie: You would have to pick her?
杰森:如果你不高兴的话,那我去帮朱迪.
Jason: I'll help Judy if that would make you happy.
麦琪:没有不高兴啊.额尔,请去帮一个默特好么?
Maggie: Very.Earl, would you help Murtle please.
额尔:哦.
Earl: Oh (sprays breath fresher)
朱迪:麦琪,请允许我说一句,
Judy: Maggie.May I say, in the calm before the storm, that,
你对于所有在场的其它母亲而言,都是一种鼓舞.
well you're an inspiration to all the other mothers.
工作,家庭,孩子,
Balancing a career, kids, this carnival.Oh, what a gal!
还有这次的狂欢节,都能协调兼顾,
It is so wonderful to meet someone at lifes banquet,
有条不紊.能遇到您真是三生有幸.
who is able to dish up another helping.
女孩:看这帮人.他们还觉得他们这么做都是为我们好.
Girl: Look at them.They think they are doing all this for us.
本:对.
Ben: Yeah.
女孩:他们确实是在为我们好.
Girl: And they are really doing it for themselves.
本:对!
Ben: Yeah!
女孩:其实是为了自己,臭显.
Girl: Blatant self aggrandizement.
本:对.
Ben: Yeah.
女孩:让人恶心.
Girl: It's disgusting.
本:你妈妈是哪一个?
Ben: Which mother's yours?
女孩:长得有点像玛瑞安的那位,你母亲是哪一位?
Girl: the one that looks like Marianne from Gilligan's island.Which one is yours?
本:那个对我视而不见的.
Ben: The one who's ignoring me.
甚至飞镖那边她也没让我管,总是说我办事没谱儿.
She wouldn't even let me run the dart booth,
玛瑞安是哪一个?
just because she said I'm so unpredictable.Which one was Marianne?
麦琪:第一次,第二次,成交.请您健康使用,
Maggie: Going once.Going twice.Sold.Use it in good health sir.
先生.好了,下面是我们最后的一个动物拍卖品.还剩下什么了,
Well that's our last animal item.What do we have left Gale?
格尔?哦,有人刚刚捐助了一个可爱的陶制项链,其中有我本人的照片.
Oh, somebody donated a little clay cameo.With my picture in it.Let's start...
现在开始……不,我的照片.这东西从哪儿来的,格尔?
No, my picture.Where did this come from Gale?
格尔:刚才在箱子里.
Gale: It was in the box.
麦琪:本.
Maggie: Ben.
男人:一块钱.
Man: A buck.
麦琪:稍等.
Maggie: Just a minute.
女士:两块.
Lady: Two bucks.
格尔:呵!
Gale: Ho!
麦琪:这个我不能卖.
Maggie: I can't sell this.
男人:两块半.
Man: Two fifty
格尔:呵!
Gale: Ho!
女士:五块.
Lady: Five bucks.
麦琪:这是非卖品..
Maggie: This is not for sale.
男人:十块.
Man: Ten.
格尔:呵!
Gale: Ho!
麦琪:十二.
Maggie: Twelve.
女士:十五.
Lady: Fifteen.
麦琪:十六.
Maggie: Sixteen.
男人:十七.
Man: Seventeen.
格尔:呵!
Gale: Ho!
麦琪:二十.
Maggie: Twenty.
女士:嗨.
Lady: Hey.
麦琪:二十五.
Maggie: Twenty five.
麦琪:麦琪!
Gale: Maggie!
麦琪:三十.
Maggie: Thirty.
格尔:停.
Gale: Stop.
麦琪:三十五.第一次,第二次,成交.
Maggie: Thirty five.Going once, going twice, sold!
格尔:好了好了好了!那,38号双碟胸罩,我的起始叫价应该是多少?
Gale: Alrighty righty righty!So what's my opening bid for a box of size 38 double
d braziers
男人:1000块钱.
Man: One thousand dollars.
格尔:成交.
Gale: Sold.
迈克:末日审判.第五张,也是最后一张了.
Mike: Ok, judgment day.Fifth and final card.The seven from heaven.Wow.
七,简直天赐的啊.哇,三个同花.
Three of a kind.A ten.Lousy luck, ride the garbage truck.And a Jake.
What does that make?Two pair, life's not fair.And an ace for the ace
那能凑成多少?两对,命运在捉弄人.庄家又赢了.
Another full boat.Dealer wins again.
好了,谨代表所有小朋友,我向你表示感谢.
And on behalf of all the little children, I thank you.
麦琪:迈克,你看到本了么?
Maggie: Mike, have you seen Ben?
迈克:看到了,他来过,把他所有的票都留给了我.
Mike: Yeah, he came by and gave me all his tickets.
麦琪:他为什么那么做?
Maggie: Why would he do that?
迈克:妈妈,本做的事情很少能让人想得通.
Mike: Mum, very little of what Ben does makes sense.
麦琪:最好我还是跟开萝尔核实一下.
Maggie: I better check with Carol.
迈克:好主意.她跟他一样怪.
Mike: Yeah, good idea.She's just as weird as he is.
开萝尔:这么看,
Carol: Well, look at it this way.
如果你
If you can't eat it you could strip your furniture with it.
麦琪:开萝尔,本有来过来么?
Maggie: Carol, has Ben been around here?
开萝尔:就来过一会儿,和其它人一样,妈妈.闻闻这个.
Carol: Just for a second.Same as everybody else mum.Smell this stuff.
麦琪:他说过什么么?
Maggie: Did he say anything?
开萝尔:他管我要家里钥匙来着.
Carol: Well, he asked for my house key.
麦琪:他说原因了么?
Maggie: Did he say why?
开萝尔:他可能说了,不过我没听清,这辣椒可能影响了我的听力.
Caro: l He may have.You know I think this chilly is effecting my hearing.
麦琪:杰森!
Maggie: Jason!
杰森:现在不行,亲爱的,我有点……(跌入水中)你想干什么?
Jason: Not now honey.I'm a little...(falls in water) So what did you want?
麦琪:亲爱的,本有没有跟你说回家的事儿?
Maggie: Honey, did Ben say anything to you about going home?
杰森:没.
Jason: No.
麦琪:不,他说过.他把票给了迈克,问开萝尔要的钥匙.
Maggie: Well he did.He gave Mike his tickets and got Carols key.
杰森:怎么会这样,没道理啊.他不会落下他自己的狂欢节的.
Jason: That doesn't make any sense.He wouldn't miss his own carnival.
麦琪:杰森,我在跟你说话呢.
Maggie: Jason, I'm talking to you.
杰森:我在听着呢,我正在听着呢.
Jason: I'm listening.I'm listening.
麦琪:看看这个.他做的项链,
Maggie: Look at this.His cameo that he made for my picture.
为放我的照片做的.我刚才从拍卖箱里找到的.
I found it in the auction box.
杰森:可能这是他自己的方式,想告诉你些什么.
Jason: Well, you know.Maybe that's just his way of telling you something.
麦琪:比方什么?
Maggie: Like what?
杰森:我不知道,亲爱的.你得自己想.孩子们交流的方式都不一样.他们……(跌入水中)你得自己琢磨所有可能的方式……麦琪!
Jason: I don't know honey.You got to think.Kids have different ways to try
to communicate.They...(falls in water) You just have to explore every
possible way... Maggie
播放歌曲:差一刻就三点了,这个地方空无一人,
Song playing: Its quarter to three.There's no one in the place.
只有你我.
Except you and me.So set them up Jo.I got a little story.
麦琪:本杰明*希佛.
Maggie: Benjamin Seaver.
本:妈妈,你去哪儿了?
Ben: Mum.Where have you been?
麦琪:在狂欢节上,本,直到我发现你一句话没说就走了.
Maggie: At your carnival Ben.Until I found out you left without a word.
本:你那阵子很忙.
Ben: You were busy.
麦琪:本,我再忙也有时间给你.
Maggie: Bennie.I am never too busy for you.
本:妈妈,几个小时前我就离开了,而你,现在才回来.
Ben: Mum, I left hours ago.And you show up now.
麦琪:所以,你是想让我着急,是么?
Maggie: So you wanted to worry me?
本:我是想要样儿东西.
Ben: I wanted something.
麦琪:所以你把这个给扔了?
Maggie: Is that why you got rid of this?
本:我刚刚还在纳闷它到哪儿去了.
Ben: I was wondering where that went.
麦琪:我在拍卖箱里找到了.
Maggie: Well I found it in the auction box.
本:怎么回跑到那儿?
Ben: How did it get there?
麦琪:是因为你想让找到它,而后跑回家,是么?
Maggie: So you wanted me to find it and come running home?
本:不,我想让你想我,而后跑回家.
Ben: No.I wanted you to miss me and come running home.
麦琪:本,狂欢节上有300号人.
Maggie: Ben, there were three hundred people there.
本:我知道.但是你十岁的心肝只有一个.
Ben: Yeah.But only one who's your most favorite ten year old on the planet.
麦琪:宝贝,你知道我为什么报名做志愿者么?
Maggie: Honey.Why do you think I volunteered?
本:我不知道,
Ben: I don't know.
什么我也不知道,
I didn't know anything except you were a really great mom before that
我只知道你是个非常出色的妈妈----在这个破狂欢节之前.
stupid carnival.
麦琪:哦,本.
Maggie: Oh Ben.I didn't do any of this for myself.
我做的所有这些,都不是为了我.
The only one I cared about was you.
我关心的惟一的人是你.我不会埋在事堆里,
See, I'm not the kind of person who gets so wrapped up in what I'm doing,
只忙自己,然后就忘了……你.
that I'd forget about...you.Oh holy dolito!
本:喔!
Ben: Hu!
麦琪:哦,本,我其实应该向你道个歉,我没有做好一个母亲.
Maggie: Oh Ben, I owe you an apology.Talk about me being a jerk.
本:我刚才可没有那么说.
Ben: I didn't say that.
麦琪:不,可我要那么说.
Maggie: No I did.
本:哦.
Ben: Oh.
麦琪:哦,宝贝,我,我,真对不起.我,只顾细枝末节,忽略了真正重要的东西.
Maggie: Oh honey, I, I'm so sorry.I couldn't see the forest for the trees.
本:什么?
Ben: What trees?
麦琪:本,我以为,你会认为对我而言我的工作会比你还要重要.
Maggie: Ben, I thought that you thought my work was more important to
事实上,我以为你会那么认为,
me than you.But what I thought you thought, you never thought,
可是,你从来没有那样认为过;而你以为我会这样认为,我从来没这样认为过.
and what you thought I thought, I never thought.
本:那我们一直在想的是什么?
Ben: What were we thinking?
播放歌曲:为了我们的孩子,为了道路的建设.
Song playing: Make it one for my baby.And one more for the road.
迈克:好了!让我们听听这个打水球的姑娘是怎么说的吧.连续38个.
Mike: Alright!Lets here it for the little spit baller with pigtails.Alright!That's thirty eight in a row.
女孩:37.下一个才是第38个.
Girl: Thirty seven.This next one will be thirty eight.
迈克:狂欢节已接近尾声,可不要口袋里揣着奖券回家哦,你们可以在这里把它们贡献出来.
Mike: Ok, now carnivals almost over folks.We don't want you to go home with any coupons in your pockets, so you can help out over here and sink a
shrink for charity
杰森:嗨,朱迪,
Jason: Hey Judy.I'm out of here Judy.
我得走了,朱迪.你得找个人替我.
You're going to have to find another sinkee.
所有人:不行!
Everyone: Boo!
迈克:得了,爸爸,没忘吧,这么做都是为了一件大善事.
Mike: Come on dad.Remember this is all for a very good cause.
杰森:我知道,你想怎么着?想坐我的位置?
Jason: I know that.You what?You want to take my place.
所有人:欢迎.
Everyone: Applause.
杰森:好,女士们,先生们,就一块钱.75分,50分,我想借你们一块钱.请上前面来.女士们,先生们,试试运气?
开萝尔:哦,让我来,行么?我是他妹妹.
Jason: So ladies and gentlemen, just one dollar.Seventy five cents, fifty cents, I'll loan you a dollar.Step right up here.My money is your shot.Go ahead and
dunk a punk.Yes ladies and gentlemen.Go for it! Carol Ah, may I try
I'm his sister